大家好，欢迎各位美女收看这个视频。
Hello you beautiful people are welcome to this video.
现在，您将学习通配符，而不是拥有一个很棒的名称。
Well you're going to be learning about wildcards now other than having an awesome name.
通配符是非常有用的工具，可以使您的命令更精确、更有表现力
Wild cards are very useful tools that will make your commands a lot more precise a lot more expressive
而且要强大得多。
and a lot more powerful.
现在，在本课程中，您将了解最常见的通配符类型，并了解如何
Now in this lecture you're going to learn about the most common types of wildcards and you'll see how
它们对于在Linux中操作文件非常有用。
they can be very useful for manipulating files in Linux.
在视频结束时，您将了解如何使用一些最常见的墙卡类型，您还可以
By the end of the video you'll know how to use some of the most common types of wall cards and you also
能够创建更强大的命令。
have the ability to create more powerful commands.
所以，让我们继续直截了当地谈吧。
So let's go ahead and get right into it.
好的。
OK.
因此，首先让我们再看一下L s命令，现在ls命令将列出每个
So first let's take a look again at the L s command now the ls command will list the contents of every
我们为其提供有效路径的目录。
directory that we give it a valid path to.
例如，假设我们想要列出Documents目录的内容。
So for example let's say we wanted to list the contents of our documents directory.
我们可以使用ls，然后给它一个指向我们的文档目录的路径。
We could do ls and then give it a path to our documents directory.
好的，当你在劈开上发微博的时候，我们可能会加上一些制表符补全，然后让它列出我们的文档
OK so when you slash that maybe we'd throw in a bit of tab completion and get it to list our documents
或者，如果我们已经在主文件夹中，就像您现在看到的那样，我们可以只说LIST LIST OUT
or if we're already in our home folder like we are now as you can see we could just say list list out
文件，这样就可以了。
documents and that will do fine.
但是，如果我们想要查看Documents文件夹、Downloads文件夹和
But what if we wanted to have a look at what's inside our documents folder our downloads folder and
我们的图片文件夹同时打开。
our Pictures folder at the same time.
很明显，在屏幕上我们这样做的方式是，我们只说不到文档，有点厚颜无耻的Tab键顺序
Well it's clear the screen the way we do that is we just say less than documents bit of cheeky tab order
完成下载一些厚颜无耻的Tabata完成和一些带有一些厚颜无耻的Tabel的图片到
completion downloads bit of cheeky Tabata completion and some pictures with a bit of cheeky tabel to
完成，然后如果我们现在继续，您会看到我们实际上可以看到每个
completion and then if we go ahead right now you'll see that we can actually see the contents of each
列出的目录。
directory listed.
到目前一切尚好。
So far so good.
但是您可以看到这个过程是如何手动进行的，这就是在哪里键入文档，然后键入Downloads
But you can see how manual of a process this was right where to type out documents then type out downloads
然后键入图片，即使用Tabel来完成，以便将它们作为公共参数传递
and then type at pictures even with even with tabel to completion in order to pass them as common arguments
添加到ls命令。
to the ls command.
现在，通配符基本上是特殊符号，shell将其解释为具有特殊含义。
Now wildcards are basically special symbols that the shell interprets to have a special meaning.
通配符背后的想法是构建称为正则表达式的强大模式，以便
The idea behind wildcards is to build up powerful patterns known as regular expressions so that instead
在手动键入每个命令行参数的情况下，您可以说类似于嘿Linux make
of typing out every command line argument manually you can instead say something like hey linux make
此命令作用于与此模式匹配的任何内容。
this command act on anything that matches this pattern.
这些模式称为正则表达式，您可以将通配符视为一些有用的
The patterns are known as regular expressions and you can think of wildcards as being some of the useful
用于创建正则表达式和使用通配符构建正则表达式的构建块提供了
building blocks for creating regular expressions and using wildcards to build regular expressions gives
您可以非常灵活地控制命令的工作方式，并且可以省去大量的打字工作
you lots of flexibility and control of how your commands work and can save you a whole bunch of typing
使用正则表达式可以确保命令更具表现力。
and using regular expressions make sure commands a lot more expressive.
例如，不是像这样表示ls命令，而是列出此文件夹的内容，如下所示
So for example instead of expressing the ls command like list out the contents of this folder and this
文件夹和这个文件夹，这是我们通常使用它的方式，不带逗号和参数，对吧
folder and this folder which is the way that we would usually be using it with comma non-arguments right
我们会说LS做文档、下载和图片下载器、下载和图片。
we'd be saying LS Do documents and downloads and pictures downloaders down downloads and pictures.
好的。
OK.
这就是它的运作方式。
That's how it works.
您必须手动列出它们。
You've got to list them manually.
相反，您可以只做一些类似的操作，比如不会使用列出每个文件开始的内容
Instead you could just do something like hey wouldn't use list out the contents of every file starts
字母D
with the letter D.
例如，如果您要删除文件，而不是说删除此文件，今年秋天和今年秋天
For example if you're removing files instead of saying remove this file and this fall and this fall
例如，您可以说删除此文件夹中的每个文件，只要其名称以datti xti结尾即可。
you can say remove every file in this folder as long as its name ends in Datti XTi for example.
或者，如果您要复制文件，而不是在此文件中说复制此文件，您可以说复制间隔
Or if you're copying files instead of saying copy this file this far in this file you can say copy every
只要文件名以Dot PTF Case结尾，即可将文件从此文件夹复制到此另一个文件夹。
file from this folder and to this other folder as long as its name ends with Dot PTF case.
现在我们明白了，我们正在使用通配符来构建这些模式，这些正则表达式。
So now that we understand that we're using wild cards to build these patterns these regular expressions.
让我们开始使用通配符构建一些正则表达式。
Let's start building some regular expressions using wildcards.
然后最常用的通配符之一是星号或星号通配符。
And then one of the most used wildcards is the asterisk or the star wildcard.
现在我通过按Shift键和键盘上的8键来找到星星，这是8个班次中的第一个班次。
Now I find the star by pressing shift and eight on my keyboard the first shift in eight.
如果你用过Microsoft Accelerate，你知道一个软件电子表格包，我就会看到星号。
I get the star come up if you ever use Microsoft accelerate you know a software spreadsheet package.
这是你用来做乘法的符号。
It's the symbol you use to do multiplication.
但是我发现在我的键盘上使用Shift和8可能与你的有所不同，但就这么简单
But I find that using shift and 8 on my keyboard it might be different on yours but it's that simple
我们现在要找的是通配符。
we're looking for now wildcards.
每个匹配特定的模式，星号或星通配符匹配任何一段文本
Each match a specific pattern and the asterisk or the star wildcard matches any piece of text regardless
该文本的长度，并且它也与数字匹配。
of the length of that text and it also matches numbers.
因此，假设我们想要检查主文件夹中每个目录的内容。
So let's say that we wanted to check the contents of every directory in the home folder.
让我清理一下屏幕。
Let me clear the screen.
如果我播放屏幕，而不是全部列出，好的，因为这里有相当多的折叠，对吧
If I play the screen instead of listing them all out OK because it's quite a few folds in here right
而不是说OK LS桌面、文档和下载等等。
instead of saying OK LS desktop and documents and downloads and so on and so on.
我们所要做的就是做lsstar。
All we have to do is just do ls star.
好的，如果我按下它，如果我按了，你可以看到它只是列出了家里的所有东西
OK so if I press it if I do that you can see that it is just listed out all of the contents of the home
文件夹、桌面文档、下载音乐、图片、公共模板和视频一气呵成。
folder the desktop documents downloads music pictures public templates and videos all in one go.
所以我们要清空屏幕。
So we clear the screen.
好的。
OK.
那这是怎么发生的。
So how did that happen.
发生这种情况的原因是因为商店匹配任何东西。
The reason that happened is because the store matches anything.
好的，所以你需要考虑的是，当你给一个命令一个正则表达式来使用的时候。
OK so you will you need to think of is when you give a command a regular expression to work with.
想象一下将其作为命令行参数。
Imagine it putting as command line arguments.
任何符合这个模式的东西。
Anything that matches that pattern.
好的。
OK.
因此，因为星通配符匹配任何内容，所以它将所有内容作为命令行参数放入LS
So because the star wildcard matches anything it puts everything as command line arguments to the LS
指挥部。
command.
这事儿可以理解。
That makes sense.
我们再举一个例子。
Let's take another example.
好的，假设我只想列出以D开头的文件夹的内容。
OK so let's say I just wanted to list the contents of the folders starting with D.
所以桌面下载和文档文件夹。
So the desktop downloads and documents folders.
好的。
OK.
我能做的是，我可以说，好的，让我们做不到大写的D，然后是一个星号。
What I can do is I could say OK let's do less than a capital D and then a star.
现在的模式是这样的。
Now the pattern is this bit.
好的，图案是D，他们是星星。
OK the pattern is the D them the star.
好的。
OK.
星号是带有字母D的积木之一。
And the star is one of the building blocks with the letter D.
所以我们在这里说的是listo，然后把它作为命令参数，任何有D a大写的东西
So what we're saying here is listo then giving it as a command argument anything that has a D a capital
d，然后跟任何东西。
D and then followed by anything.
所以基本上所有以大写D开头的东西。
So basically anything that starts with a capital D.
如果我这样做，您可以看到我们只看到桌面文档和下载，您可以看到
So if I do the you can see that we just see the desktop documents and downloads and you can see that
它们都与这个图案相匹配，这个D-Star，它们以大写D开头，如果后面跟任何东西
they all match this pattern this D-Star they start with a capital D and then if followed by anything
它们以大写D开头，然后跟任何字母。
they start with a capital D and then are followed by anything.
如果我们只想要文档和下载呢？
What if we just want documents and downloads.
嗯，它们以d‘eau开头，然后是任何正确的东西。
Well they start with d'eau and then followed by anything right.
所以如果我做ls D O，那么你能看到的任何东西，我们只得到文档和下载。
So if I do ls D O then anything you can see we just get documents and downloads.
但是桌面会被忽略。
But desktop is ignored.
这里需要记住的重要一点是，这些通配符和这些正则表达式
Now something that is important to remember here is that these wild cards and these regular expressions
区分大小写。
are case sensitive.
所以，如果我们做了LS D，然后Savoned有DS小写，你可以看到我们什么也得不到，什么也得不到
So if we did LS D and then astonied does have the DS lowercase you can see that we get nothing nothing
返回是因为所有内容都不以小写D开头。
comes back because nothing starts with the lowercase D.
但是如果我们做大写B。
But if we do capital B.
现在这样就行了。
Now that will work OK.
所以这真的很棒。
So that's really awesome.
让我来清理一下屏幕，您已经看到了明星通配符可以用来匹配任何
Let me just clear the screen you've seen a few ways that the star wild card can be used to match any
文本，您已经看到了它可以用来构建正则表达式的一些方法。
text and you've seen some ways that it can be used to build regular expressions.
现在，在使用正则表达式时，您可能会使用其他一些常用通配符
Now there are a few other common wild cards that you'll likely use when working with regular expressions
还有通配符。
and wild cards.
第一个是问号通配符。
And the first is the question mark wildcard.
现在星通配符将匹配任何内容，而不考虑长度。
Now the star wildcard will match anything regardless of length.
例如，如果我做像Stardock T-Rex t这样的事情，只要它结束，就可以匹配任何东西
So for example if I do something like Stardock T-Rex t that could match anything as long as it ends
因为如果我从60开始，你会看到我们只看到以点T结尾的东西。
in Dot XTi t because if I do ls start up to 60 you'll see that we only see things that end in dot T.
X-Take。
X take.
现在，如果在取t之前出现的开头是1都无关紧要，更不用说
Now it doesn't matter if what at the beginning of the of the comes before that takes t is 1 let alone
一个数字长，或者你知道一百个字母长，总是充满数字或其他无关紧要的东西
1 number long or you know a hundred letters long always full of numbers or whatever it doesn't matter
如果它有一千个字符，但仍然匹配，因为星号可以匹配任何内容。
if it's a thousand characters long and it'll still match because the star matches anything.
但是问号通配符只能匹配一个位置。
But the question mark wildcard will only match one place.
所以如果我这么做了。
So if I do.
问号。
Question mark.
西蒂医生。
Dr. XTi.
好的，如果我现在这样做，什么都不会出现。
OK if I do ls now nothing will actually show up.
好的。
OK.
因为问题是这样的。
Because the question is this.
这基本上说明了这说明的是。
This says basically what this says is.
所以任何以点结尾的东西都需要t，但在它之前只有一件事。
So anything that ends in Dot takes t but only has one thing before it.
好的。
OK.
所以这将与点txti或提示高达60，或Elda T-Rex T或1.60相匹配。
So this would match things like a dot t XTi or cued up to 60 or Elda T-Rex T or 1.60.
好的，你注意到他们都只有一个位置，就在Datti XTi之前。
OK you notice how they've all just got one place just before the Datti XTi.
好的。
OK.
问号是一种方式，表示它就像是星星所在位置的占位符。
The question mark is a way of saying it's like a placeholder for just that place where's the star.
有多长时间并不重要。
It doesn't matter how long it is.
因此，问号通配符允许您保持星型通配符的通用性，因为它
So the question mark wild card allows you to maintain the generality of the star wildcard because it
不管它匹配什么，它可以匹配一个数字，也可以匹配一个字母。
doesn't matter what it matches it can match a number or it can match a letter.
但它允许您限制长度。
But it allows you to limit the length.
好的，明星没有长度限制。
OK the star doesn't put a limit on length.
问号在哪里。
Where's the question mark.
是的，但用什么填满那个地方其实并不重要。
Does but it doesn't really matter what fills that place.
好的。
OK.
现在，当您想要构建常规模式但又关心以下内容时，通常会使用问号通配符
Now you usually use the question mark wildcard when you want to build a general pattern but care about
文件名的长度。
the length of the filename.
好的，如果我们做一些类似问号、问号、PTF的事情，那么就会匹配像1这样的东西
OK so if we did something like question mark question mark PTF then that would match things like a 1
点PDA或B2或PTF或AID或PTF，或者你知道的ZED，7点PTF或类似7：7点的百科。
dot PDA or B2 or PTF or aid or PTF or you know Zed seven dot PTF or something like 7:7 dot pedia.
您可以看到我们只占用了两个空间，然后没有PTF，这就是问号时钟问号
You see how we're just taking up two spaces and then not PTF that's what question clock question mark
或者PTF也行。
or PTF would do.
好的，我们说我们要用两样东西填满它。
OK we're saying we're going to fill it with two things.
两个空间，我们不确定它会不会到那里，但肯定有两个空间，两个地方。
Two spaces we're not sure it's going to go there but there's got to be two spaces two places.
然后是PTF。
And then PTF.
好的。
OK.
所以这就是它的工作原理。
So that's how that works.
这是现在的问号。
That's the question mark now.
另一种类型的通配符称为方括号，这里的方括号就是这些。
Another type of wild card is called is the square brackets which are these ones here.
这里的方括号。
The square brackets here.
好的。
OK.
方括号通配符与问号相似，因为它只匹配一个位置。
And the square brackets wildcard is similar to the question mark in that it will only match one place.
但是，不匹配问号之类的内容，将只允许使用方括号中的模式
But instead of matching anything like the question mark will square brackets allow only allow the pattern
更具体地说，只有在字母或数字属于给定集合时才匹配它们
to be there to be more specific and only match the letters or numbers if they belong to a given set
一系列的选择。
of options.
对我来说展示可能比解释容易。
Probably easier for me to show than to explain.
好的。
OK.
假设我们有6个文件作为文本，我们有文件B DirectX t，我们有Falce Dotty x t，我们是
So say we had six files we had for a text we had file B directx t we had falce Dotty x t and we are
2.6T跟踪1.60，3.6D跟踪。
followed 1.60 for 2.6 T and for 3.6 D.
好的，哪个意图。
OK which intent.
如果我这样做了，除非我们的主目录中实际上已经有这些文件。
If I do unless we actually already have those in a in our home directory.
好的。
OK.
因此，假设我们想要匹配文件名中只包含数字的文件。
So let's say we wanted to match the files that just had numbers in the filename.
因此，对于1.60，2.2XTi和3.6。
So for 1.60 for 2.2 XTi and for 3.6.
但我们不想让Abian同意这样做，我们可以做的比提交更少，因为
But we don't want the ones that have Abian say OK to do this we could do less than file because the
名称必须以file开头，然后打开方括号，给它一堆选项。
name's got to start with file then open the square brackets and give it a bunch of options.
我们可以说12，3，4，5，6，7，8，9，0点文本。
We could say 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 0 dot text.
好的，这是什么。
Ok so what's this.
基本上，这些方括号中的所有东西都是一个可以填补这个位置的选项。
Basically everything in these square brackets is an option that could fill that one place.
所以任何文件都会被归档，然后是1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 0，其中任何一个都是Dotti XTi案例，如果
So anything goes file and then either 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 0 0 any one of those then Dotti XTi case if
我们这样做了，你看，我们得到了4，1，4，2和4，3，但是我们没有得到A，B和C，因为它们不是
we do that you see that we get 4 1 4 2 and 4 3 but we don't get the A B and C because they're not part
所有选择中的一部分。
of the options.
正确的。
Right.
从一组仅与一个Faltu和所有三个Faltu匹配的文件中提取。
From a given set of files that just matches for one Faltu and for all three.
但我不想让你知道这怎么可能用星号通配符或
But I don't want you to know is how this wouldn't be possible using either the star wildcard or the
如果我们这样做，请使用问号通配符。
question mark wildcard if we do.
最后一个问号t问号将与任何内容匹配。
LS final question mark t the question mark will match anything.
好的，但只有一个地方。
AK but only one place.
如果我们拍明星的话你会看到的。
If we do the star you're going to get though.
我需要LSN，你也会得到基本上相同的东西，因为这些不会限制
I need to LSN you're going to get basically the same thing as well because these don't restrict what
去那个地方。
goes in that place.
不管长短，这批货什么都有。
The stock will have anything regardless of length.
问号只需要一个位置，但它并不关心是什么填满了它。
The question mark will need just one place but it doesn't care what fills it.
方括号也只有一个位置，但它们允许您限制去那里的内容。
The square brackets also only have one place but they allow you to restrict what goes there.
所以他们就像是最严格的，就像是一种非常严格的沃克哈特。
So they're like the most restrictive it's like a very restrictive kind of kind of Wockhardt.
现在您可能已经注意到，键入所有这些数字0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9有点麻烦
Now you may have noticed that typing out all these numbers 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 is a bit of a hassle
正确的。
right.
所以舒姆让我们的比赛变得更容易了。
So the Schum makes it a bit easier for us.
我们有一条从0到9的捷径，这给了我们完全相同的东西。
We've got a shortcut we can do for 0 to 9 and that gives us exactly the same thing.
因此，不必键入所有的数字，这要容易得多。
So instead of having to type out all the numbers it's it's much easier.
当您想要使用字母表时，这真的很有用，您可以继续操作，这将
Which is really useful for when you want to work with the alphabet and you can go ahead and that will
工作完全正常。
work perfectly OK.
如果你想刻上两位数呢。
What if you want to notched two digits.
好的，那么如果您想要类似于文件11的内容，那又如何呢？
OK so what if you wanted something like file 11.
好的。
OK.
我该怎么做呢。
How would I do that.
好的，你这样做的方法是，你会说LS文件，然后今晚的第一个数字是0，然后再给它一个数字
Well the way you do that is you'd say LS file then for the first digit 0 tonight then just give it another
一个0到9，然后是Datti Xti。
one zero to nine then Datti XTi.
好的。
OK.
所以这个数字变成了第一个数字。
So this one becomes the first digit.
这个数字变成第二个数字。
This one becomes the second digit.
如果我想要一个数字，然后是一个字母呢？
What if I wanted to have a number and then a letter.
嗯，那很简单。
Well that's easy.
把它改成字母就行了。
Just change that to letters.
如果我想要一个数字，然后是一个字母，然后是一个小写字母，那怎么办？
What if I wanted to have a number then a letter then a lowercase letter.
这个简单的改变就像那样。
Well that simple change that like that.
您可以看到In文件。
And you can see the in file.
然后是一个可以有数字0到9的空格，然后是另一个可以有数字0到9的空格
Then one space which can have the number zero to nine then another space which can have the number of
字母8先添加大写字母，然后添加另一个空格，该空格可以将字母8作为‘ad’小写
the letters 8 is adding uppercase then another space which can have the letters eight As'ad in lowercase
然后以Dotti X Take结尾。
and then ends in Dotti X take.
因此，只需添加几个简单的通配符，您就可以看到这些正则表达式可以变得多么强大。
So you can see just how powerful these regular expressions can become just by adding a few simple wildcards.
如果我们想要数字0到9，也可以有字母A、B和C，您可以这样做吗
We could also what if we wanted to have the numbers 0 to 9 but also the letters A B and C you can do
那也是一样的。
that as well.
简单得不得了。
Just like that.
而这一点将会出现在Shope中，这正是你所期待的。
And that's going to show up in Shope exactly what you'd expect.
任何有单词file的东西。
Anything that has the word file.
然后从0到9或者字母A、B和C中的一个大写，然后不给我发短信。
Then one of the numbers from 0 to 9 or the letters A B and C and uppercase then not text me.
如果我将其缩小为小写ABC，他们将只得到4、1、2和3，因为这些通配符和
If I reduce that to lowercase ABC they will just get 4 one two and three because these wildcards and
这些组织区分大小写。
these organizations are case sensitive.
所以你可以看到非常非常强大的家伙的疯狂原因。
So you can see wild cause of really really powerful stuff guys.
你真正需要知道的只有三个，那就是匹配任何东西的那颗星。
And the the only three that you really need to know are the star which matches anything.
仅从一个位置匹配任何内容的问号和允许的方括号
The question mark which matches anything but only from one place and the square brackets which allow
你只需要匹配一个地方。
you to match just one place.
但他们也喜欢定义什么是匹配的。
But they also like to define what matches.
好了，现在的通配符好就到此为止。
OK so that's enough wild card goodness for now.
通配符可以使您的命令更具表现力，并使您能够更好地控制
Wild Cards can make your commands a lot more expressive and give you much greater control over how the
命令是有效的，以这种方式使用通配符搜索文件名实际上有一个他妈的有趣的名字。
commands work and using wildcards in this way to search for filenames actually has a fucking funny name.
这就是所谓的投球。
And it's called globbing.
因此，如果您曾经听到单词globping在它周围漂浮，那么它的意思就是使用通配符来查找文件
So if you ever hear the word globbing floating around it just means using wildcards to look for file
名字就像我们在这段视频中所做的那样，所以在结束之前，请快速回顾一下我们所做的
names just like we've done in this video so before closing out just take a quick recap of what we've
学到了东西。
learned.
首先，您将了解正则表达式的概念，正则表达式基本上是模式
First you learn about the concept of regular expressions and regular expressions are basically patterns
一段文字需要匹配。
that a piece of text needs to match.
好的。
OK.
任何与该模式匹配的内容都将作为命令行参数传递给命令。
And anything that matches that pattern will be passed as a command line argument to the command.
现在星通配符匹配任何内容，而不考虑长度。
Now the star wildcard matches anything regardless of length.
问号匹配任何位置，而不是只匹配一个位置，方括号只匹配一个位置
The question mark matches anything but just for one place and the square brackets match just one place
但允许您指定您知道将实际匹配的选项。
but allow you to specify options that you know will actually be matched.
因此，与问号中的开头匹配任何内容不同，方括号始终是您选择的
So unlike the start in the questionmark which will match anything the square brackets alays you choose
什么会是匹配的。
what will be match.
当然，您也可以只键入您特别想要显示的字母和数字。
And of course you can just type letters and numbers in that you want specifically to appear as well.
所以如果我用大写D，那么start就意味着任何以D开头的东西，然后是后面的任何东西。
So if I did capital D then start that means anything that starts with a D and then has anything afterwards.
你也可以在里面输入字母和数字。
You can type letters and numbers in there as well.
您不需要只使用星号和方括号。
You don't just have to only use the star questionmark and square brackets.
好的，理解了通配符之后，您就有了学习不同方法的非常坚实的基础
OK so with wildcards understood you have a very solid foundation for learning about the different ways
操作文件系统中的文件。
to manipulate files in the file system.
主要用于创建、删除、移动、复制和粘贴文件等命令。
Major the commands to create delete move copy and paste files and so on.
它实际上相当简单，当你学习它们的时候，你可能会想知道真正学习的意义是什么
It's actually rather simple and when you learn them you might wonder what's the point of actually learning
如何使用它们，而不仅仅是指向和单击。
how to use them instead of just pointing and clicking.
但是，通过了解如何结合使用这些命令和通配符，您将能够操作数百个
But by knowing how to use these commands along with wildcards you'll be able to manipulate hundreds
在完全控制的情况下，指向和点击很快就会看起来像这样
of files at once and with complete control to the point the pointing and clicking will soon seem like
一种非常缓慢和迟缓的做事方式。
a very slow and sluggish way of doing things.
相信我。
Believe me.
因此，接下来您可以进行一个快速测验来帮助您巩固对通配符的理解，因为您
So up next you can have a quick quiz to help you cement your understanding of wildcards because you
要知道熟能生巧。
know practice makes perfect.
然后，您要领导的下一个视频必须使用一些新命令创建文件和目录
And then the next video you're going to lead had to create files and directories using some new commands
您还将把这些命令与通配符结合起来，使它们更加强大。
and you're also going to combine those commands with wildcards to make them even more powerful.
您甚至会了解到一种称为支撑扩展的东西，它将向您展示如何
You'll even learn about something called brace expansion which will see which will show you how you
仅使用一个或两个命令即可创建3个文件夹，每个文件夹包含100个文件。
can create 3 folders with 100 files in each of them using just one or two commands.
不要相信我。
Don't believe me.
好的，我想我会在下一个视频中见到你。
Well I guess I'll see you in the next video.